饥饿
的青春
第二季  第十九集
0,0,0,fx,学习
0,0,0,fx,分享
0,0,0,fx,进步
本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译
最新下载请登录www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译   冰蓝   啾啾
翻译  贝壳说爱我
校对  爱我
时间轴 贝壳说爱我
后期 斯人       总监 爱我
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
早上好
Good morning.
加比  不管你在做什么  请做两份
Gabi, whatever you're making, please make it for two.
哪个姑娘这么幸运啊
Oh, wow. Who's the lucky lady?
或者是先生
Or gentleman.
先别评判嘛
Let's not judge now.
加比  这是我弟弟杰克
Gabi, this is my younger brother, Jake.
杰克  这是加比
Jake, this is Gabi.
你好  你为什么不告诉我你弟弟要来
Oh, hello. Hi. Why didn't you tell me your brother was coming?
我不知道
I didn't know.
杰克决定在超级"常见"的凌晨三点出现
Jake decided to show up at the super conventional hour of 3:00 A.M.
他一意孤行[奔向他的鼓]
You see, he marches to his own drum...
这很搞笑  因为他是鼓手
Which is funny because he's a drummer.
曾经是
Was...
然后我成了护林员  然后在石油钻塔工作
Then I was a forest ranger, then I worked on an oil rig...
然后上了捕鲔船
then I was on a tuna boat...
结果到了泰国  而我...
that ended up in Thailand where I...
在那里玩了几个月  现在我来了
just hung out for a couple months and now I'm here.
杰克有重大新闻要说
And Jake's got big news.
他找到了他的梦想职业  告诉她
He's found his calling. Tell her.
我想做大厨
I want to be a chef.
真不错
Well, good for you!
谢谢  一开始我想当个厨师
Thanks! At first, I wanted to be a cook,
然后我想  为什么不做大厨呢
but then I thought, why not be a chef?
反正差不多  不过薪水更高
It's like the same thing, but with better pay.
实际上  并不是
Actually, you know, it's not.
成为职业大厨需要付出辛勤劳动
It takes a lot of hard work to be a professional chef.
我知道  我在飞机上看了《美食总动员》
Oh, I know. I watched Ratatouille on the plane.
答案是不
The answer is no.
这也是我的婚礼  我想...
It's my wedding, too, and I want--
杰克
Jake!
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
我听说有人要结婚了
I heard someone was getting married,
想看看我输给了谁
and I want to see who I lost out to.
天啊
My god.
你的脸蛋比上次见时还要美
You're even cheek-bonier than last time I saw you.
这是...
This is...
埃兰
Alan.
我是艾略特的未婚夫
I'm Elliot's fiance.
请不要在拍照时站在我旁边
Please never stand next to me in a photo.
加比比  问问你
Gabala, quick question.
周六你可以为我们的婚礼准备一百人的开胃菜吗
Can you make appetizers for 100 people for our wedding Saturday?
这周六吗  让我看看日程...
Uh, this Saturday, let me check my schedule...
可以
yes!
不行
No.
《造型》和《旧金山杂志》
Our wedding's being covered
都要报道我们的婚礼
by in style and San Francisco Magazine.
必须上档次
It has to be classy.
所以你懂你为什么不能做吧  加比
So you understand why you can't do it, Gabi.
你闭嘴  她很可爱的
Oh, you hush. She's adorable.
我们这是紧要关头了
And we're in a pinch.
我妈的宴会负责人
My mother's caterer...
托瓦·罗森
Tova Rosen...
在筹备晚餐  但我们需要时髦
is doing the sit down dinner, but we need cocktail apps
又有想象力的开胃小吃  而托瓦两者都不是
that are chic and whimsical and Tova is neither.
让开  托瓦
Well, move over, Tova.
因为时髦又有想象力的小吃是我的专长
'Cause chic and whimsical cocktail apps are my specialty.
加比  恭喜  我真为你高兴
Gabi, congratulations! I'm very happy for you.
同时又有点担心
And at the same time, a little concerned.
一周一百个宾客  对你来说工作量很大
Um, one week, 100 guests, that's a lot of work for one person.
很大哦
A lot of work!
你为什么要破坏我的梦想
Why are you crushing my dream?
没有
No! I'm not.
我只是建议  也许
I'm just suggesting, maybe...
你请个人来帮忙  我付钱
you hire a little extra help, my treat.
那就太棒了  谢谢
Oh, that would be great. Thank you.
真好  杰克  你找到了第一份工作
Perfect. Jake, you got your first gig.
-好棒  -不
- Yes! - No!
抱歉[意大利语]
Uh, scusi.
你刚听到了这场婚礼对我来说有多重要
You just heard how important this wedding is to me.
你真觉得一个鼓手/护林员
Do you really think that a drummer/forest ranger
适合做我的助手吗
is really the right guy to be my assistant?
你老板/付你钱的人真这么觉得
Your boss/ the person that pays you really does.
欢迎  杰克
Welcome, Jake.
我很激动/一点也不生气
I am excited/ not annoyed at all.
炖菜做好了
Okay, my stew is done.
你吃过最好吃的
The best you'll ever have.
那真是...
Wow, that's, um...
特别
something special.
我说的吧
Told you.
我觉得我有烹饪基因
I think I got the cooking gene.
好吧
Okay.
杰克  你显然靠这张脸过得很舒坦
Jake, you've obviously coasted through life on your looks,
但烹饪是习得的技能
but cooking is an acquired skill,
不是天生的  我对此很严肃
not genetic, and I take it very seriously.
你觉得我长得帅吗
You think I'm good looking?
你就听到了这句吗  这样吧
That's your takeaway? Okay, you know what?
不如你出去给我买点有机甜菜吧
Why don't you run out and get me some organic beets?
没问题
Done.
最近的市场在哪
Where's the closest market?
俄勒冈州
Oregon.
你没问过我就预定了管弦乐队吗
You booked an 11 piece band without consulting me?
我想要DJ的
I want a DJ!
你能躺在DJ的钢琴上
You can't lay across a DJ's piano
唱《大富豪》吗
and sing Big Spender, now can you?
我刚去取了婚礼穿的裙子
I just picked up my dress for the wedding.
现在你只需要请柬了
Aw, now all you need is an invitation.
他真会开玩笑
He's such a kidder.
你帮我解决了雕刻的事吧
Were you able to take care of that engraving for me?
当然  我表哥一会儿把艾略特的戒指送过来
Sure did. My cousin's dropping off Elliot's ring later today.
你俩嘀咕什么呢
What are you two whispering about?
我喜欢我为她挑选的这条裙子
Oh! Just that I love the dress I picked out for her.
你给她挑的裙子吗
You picked out her dress?
这场婚礼还有哪个部分是你没控制的吗
Is there any part of this wedding you haven't controlled?
他想让裙子搭配珊瑚色的宾客簿
He wanted it to match the coral-colored guest book.
你不了解同性恋婚礼吗
Don't you know anything about gay weddings?
我了解
Yes!
我受够了你自己做出所有决定
And I'm sick of you making all the decisions without me.
这也是人家的婚礼啊
It's my wedding, too.
你说得对  亲爱的
Oh, you're right, honey.
你来策划蜜月吧
Why don't you plan the honeymoon?
好棒  我想去夏威夷
Yay! I wanna go to Hawaii.
因为你想俗套吗
'Cause you want to be a cliche?
我是个在旧金山结婚的基佬
I am a gay man getting married in San Francisco!
老娘就是很俗啊
I am a freaking cliche!
好棒  午餐  一天最棒的时光
Yes! Lunch! Best part of the day.
喜欢吗
You like?
我让你弟弟给你做的
I let your brother make it for you.
挺好吃的
That's good.
是吗  乔什
Is it, Josh?
-真的吗  -很有潜力嘛
- Is it really? - It's got a lot of potential.
如果这是咖喱的话
If it was a curry.
加比  在你的帮助下
But, look, Gabi, with your help...
炖菜只会越来越好
the stew can only get better.
能吗  乔什
Can it, Josh?
真的能吗
Can it really?
因为这个蠢货根本对烹饪一无所知
Because this stew knows nothing about cooking,
他就要毁了我这辈子
and he's messing up my chance
最重要的一次机会
of one of the biggest opportunities of my life.
但是加比
But, Gabi...
那个蠢货是我弟弟呢
The stew is my brother.
我知道  但我想砸他的脸
I know, but I want to punch him in the freakin' face!
等等  加比
Okay, wait, Gabi.
我知道他想一出是一出
I know he's kinda all over the place,
但他好像终于找到了感兴趣的事
but it seems like he's finally found something he's excited about.
也许这就是他的梦想职业
Maybe this is his calling.
也许你该再尝尝他的炖菜
Maybe you should try another bite of his stew.
买甜菜要多久啊
How long does it take to get beets?
等我意识到俄勒冈州是个玩笑后
Well, once I realized Oregon was a joke,
就不用那么久了
not that long.
你讨厌这一切  我能感受到
You're hating this. I can feel it.
-我没有讨厌  -你就是讨厌
- I'm not hating it. - You're hating it.
我是讨厌
I'm hating it!
我得到了这辈子最大的一个机会
Okay, I've been given the biggest opportunity of a lifetime,
而我整天都在浪费时间
and I'm spending the whole day wasting it,
训练我老板的弟弟
training my boss's brother.
我懂
Look, I get it.
很抱歉  我哥哥逼你雇我
I'm sorry. My brother made you hire me.
如果你想的话  我现在就可以走
If you want, I can leave right now.
你会吗
Oh, would you?
但我真的想跟你学
But I really wanna learn from you.
为什么
Why?
为什么是我
Why me? I mean...
为什么不去学公关
Why not publicity?
艾略特肯定很高兴庇护你
I'm sure Elliot would be very happy to take you under his wing
或者压住你
or any other body part.
-你就不能先听我说完吗  -好吧
- Would you at least hear me out? - Okay.
没问题  但是你能一边擀饼皮一边聊天吗
Fine, but can you talk and roll pasta dough at the same time?
加比  问题是...
The thing is, Gabi,
乔什觉得我不定性因为我总在换工作
Josh thinks I'm a total flake because I change jobs a lot.
那的确是挺不定性的
Yeah, well, that's kind of flaky.
但我发誓这次不会了
But, I swear this time's different.
不定性的人都会这么说
Mmm, that's what flakes say.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
我终于找到了我爱的事业
I finally found something I really like.
你给的压力太大了
Okay, you're pushing too hard.
-因为你不相信我  -我是说那块面
- 'Cause I want you to believe me! - On the dough.
这可能听上去很疯狂
All right, this is gonna sound crazy,
我在泰国的时候  住在了一家寺院里
but when I was in Thailand, I ended up living in a monastery.
他们没教会你闭嘴吗
Don't they make you take a vow of silence there?
我不知道你是怎样决定成为一名厨师的
I don't know how you decided to become a chef,
但是我在寺院的时候
but when I was in the monastery,
在厨房帮忙
I got to help out in the kitchen,
为其他僧人做饭
making food for the other monks,
刚开始的时候这只是一份普通工作
and you know, at first, it was just another job...
很好  就这样轻轻地揉
Okay, that's good. That's nice and gentle.
谢谢
Thanks.
你这种专业厨师听来肯定很傻
This is gonna sound really dumb to a professional chef like you,
但是  对我来说
but, you know, for me it wasn't...
我不是热爱烹饪本身
Cooking that gave me the buzz,
而是当别人尝到我的食物时
it was the look on peoples' faces when they tasted...
脸上的表情
What I cooked.
那些僧人不会说话吧
They can't talk, can they?
我无法形容那种感觉
I wish I could put into words what that feeling was.
不用了  我懂的
No, I mean, I get it.
我也是这样爱上做饭的
That's exactly how I fell in love with cooking.
-你开玩笑吗  - 不是
- Are you kidding?  - No, I never met anybody
我从来没遇见到理解那种感觉的人
that understood that feeling before.
好了  差不多了  我来教你
Okay, you're almost there, let me show you...
往下摁  但是别太使劲
You have to push down, but not too hard.
适当用力就可以了
Okay, the right amount of pressure is key.
加比  告诉我
You gotta tell me, Gabi...
你那神奇的时刻是什么样的
When was your magical moment?
就是现在这样  什么
Now-- what?
当时你是看到了谁的表情
Whose face did you see eating your meal
让你有了那种感觉
that gave you the feeling that... that we're talking about.
是我爸爸
Um, my dad.
我和我妈
My mom and I,
以前经常一起看茱莉娅·蔡尔德的节目
we used to watch Julia Child together all the time, and...
我妈去世时  我...
When she died, I...
给他做了茱莉亚的一道菜
made him one of Julia's recipes,
我忘不了他脸上的表情
and I will never forget the look on his face.
只想永远这么做下去
You know, I just wanted to cook forever.
-什么情况  -不好意思  我太投入了
- What was that? - I'm sorry, I went with the moment.
我不知道我是怎么了
I don't know what got into me.
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
天啊  加比
Oh my God, Gabi!
今天下课以后
Today, after teaching my class,
有个妈妈跟我说了这世界上最动听的话
this mom came up to me and said the sweetest thing.
我的单车课...
My spin class...
比生孩子还痛苦
worse than childbirth.
-恭喜  -也恭喜你
- Well... congratulations. - Well, congratulations to you, too.
恭喜什么
For what?
你成功的和乔什他弟共处了一整天
For making it through the entire day with Josh's brother.
我以前从来没见过刀插眼的表情
I didn't even know they made knife-in-eye emojis.
你知道好玩的是什么吗
You know what's funny?
这一天下来...
Is that, you know, as the day went on,
我好像发现了他的另一面
I really feel like I saw a different side of him.
知道吗  他其实...
You know, he's actually a really good--
-吻技不错吗  -是
- Kisser? - Yeah.
-他亲了她  -对
- He kissed her? - Yeah.
而且她还回应了
And she kissed him back,
亲了得有三分半钟
for, like, three and a half minutes!
-好恶心  -可不是吗
- That's sick! - You're telling me.
他俩简直难舍难分
They were all over each other.
我是说你
I meant you!
他们可是在我的开放式客厅里亲
They were in my open concept living room!
问题是  尤兰达  看到他们在一起
And the thing is, Yolanda, seeing them together...
让我觉得我好像...
It made me think I still...
似乎可能还对加比有感觉
kinda might have feelings for Gabi.
"似乎可能"吗
Kinda might?
乔舒亚  这些感觉是真的
Joshua, are these feelings real
还是只是兄弟之间的竞争
or is this just some sibling rivalry?
是真的  千真万确
Real! Genuine.
我觉得
I think.
你觉得吗
You think?
你最好能肯定点
Well, you better be sure.
-因为如果不能肯定  -后果会很严重的
- Because if you're not-- - There could be seismic repercussions.
加比  杰克可是乔什的弟弟
Gabi, Jake is Josh's brother.
我知道  但我情不自禁
I know, but I can't help it.
我们有好多共同点啊
I mean, we have an amazing connection...
-比如食物  比如...  -乔什
- with food and with-- - Josh!
-加比  不行  这太复杂了  -但是...
- No, Gabi, it's too complicated! - But--
但是不行  你正在拿
But no! Look, you're risking
你与老板的关系和你的事业
your entire relationship with your boss,
冒险  而且你都不...
your career, and you're not even--
完全确定自己的感觉
100% sure how you feel.
加比不是杰克从你这儿抢走的玩具
Gabi's not just some toy Jake took from you.
你说得对
You're right.
你说得对  我确定之前是不会进一步行动的
You're right. I won't do anything until I know for sure.
我确定之前是不会进一步行动的
I won't do anything else until I know for sure.
可是会很难的
But it's gonna be really hard
因为我只想盯着他的眼睛
because all I wanna do is stare into his eyes...
夹住他的脖子
Put him in a headlock...
一遍又一遍的亲
And just kiss him over and over again.
直到他跪地求饶
Till he begs for mercy.
可怕  没品味  恶心  粗俗
Horrible, tasteless, disgusting, vile.
我说你的衣服呢  这小吃还挺好吃的
But enough about your outfit. These apps are actually delicious!
谢谢你  艾略特
Wow, thank you, Elliot.
别得意的太早
Don't get too excited.
你们得自己跟犹太公主说清楚
You're going to have to clear these with the Jewish Princess.
杰克  再见
Bye, Jake.
大家好
Oh! Hey, guys.
乔什  艾略特喜欢加比的所有小吃
Josh, Elliot loved all of Gabi's apps.
我们的小吃
Our apps.
我们是个团队嘛
We're a team.
-别闹  -你才别闹呢
- Stop! - No, you stop it!
不如你俩都别闹了
Why don't you both just kinda stop?
杰克
Hey, Jake,
来我办公室待会儿
Why don't you hang in my office?
加比把我们的时间都占了
It's like Gabi's trying to steal all our time together.
过了这么多年  做了这么多份工作
After all these years and all these jobs,
我的多面手杰克终于找到了真爱  烹饪
my Jake of all trades has finally found his trade... cooking!
我很高兴我向你证明了自己
Wow, I'm so glad I've proved myself to you.
证明你自己  可不止呢
Proved yourself? Oh, you did more than that.
你看我有多高兴  都要飞起来了
Look at me, I'm giddy. I'm downright giddy.
都是你的功劳啊
Well, I got you to thank for it.
是你给我和加比牵的线
You're the one who hooked me up with Gabi.
是啊  是我干的
Yeah! I did that.
所以我在想
So I've been thinking...
如何才能让杰克的事业越走越远
What is the best way to get Jake farther
越远  越远  越远呢
and farther and... farther in his career?
然后我想到了
And then, it hit me.
美国烹饪学院吗
The Culinary Institute of America?
这是国内最好的烹饪学校
That's the best cooking school in the country.
杰克  我动用了我所有的关系
Jake, I pulled every string I could,
才把你弄进本学期
and I got you in for this semester.
但是乔什  学费要三万六千块
But, Josh, man, it's 36 grand.
这比我的预算高了...
It's a little out of my price range by...
三万六千块
36 grand.
学费我包了  兄弟
Consider it covered, bro.
真的吗
Are you serious?
我...
I...
我真不知道说什么好
I don't know what to say.
你有这表情就够了
Your face says it all.
你在歌舞伎剧院干的那一年
You know, that year you spent studying Kabuki theater
真的有收获
really paid off.
杰克  你是我弟弟
Jake, you're my brother.
我只在完全相信的事情上投资
I only invest in things I believe in 100%,
而我完全相信你应该离开...
And I'm 100% sure you should go away...
去...上学
there... to school.
但这学校在纽约州北  还有两天就开学了
But it's in upstate New York and it starts in two days.
我来不及啊
What am I gonna do?
今晚赶紧上飞机吗
Jump on a plane tonight?
好主意
Good point.
你就只差一张...
Too bad you don't have a...
头等舱机票
first class ticket.
你好呀
Hey, you--
是你啊
Oh, it's you.
你就这么谢我
That's the thanks I get?
你借烤箱烤馅饼的时候
When you needed an extra oven
我还是你的好朋友呢
to bake your pot pies in, I was your best friend.
太感谢了  你就是救世主
Oh, I know, thank you. You're a life saver.
艾略特肯定会很开心的
Elliot's going to be so happy.
有人喜就有人悲
Well, there's a downside to everything.
我想想啊
Let me see...
你在找什么
What are you looking for?
也没什么  我不想引起什么恐慌  只不过...
Oh, nothing really. I don't want to raise any red flags, but...
你见过一枚男式婚戒吗
Have you seen a man's wedding band around here?
你把艾略特的婚戒弄丢了吗
You lost Elliot's wedding ring?
只有彻底找不到了
Ah! It's only lost...
才叫弄丢
if I don't find it.
天呐  你上一次看到它是什么时候
Oh, my god! Well, when was the last time you saw it?
"我上一次看到它是什么时候"
"When was the last time I saw it?"
你以为我没想过
You don't think I've thought,
"我上一次看到它是什么时候"吗
"when was the last time I saw it?"
我上一次看到它是什么时候
When was the last time I saw it?
为防止弄丢  我把它戴在我拇指上
I put it on my thumb because I didn't want to lose it,
然后我帮你做肉馅饼
and then I made your pot pies and...
妈蛋
Oh, my damn!
还好我饿了
Good thing I'm hungry.
-小杰  -尤兰达
- Hey, Jakey. - Hey, Yolanda.
我觉得我们该
Um, I think it would be...
聊一下昨天发生的事比较好
a good idea if we talked about what happened yesterday.
我觉得我们来聊一下
I think it would be a good idea if we talked about
我要去美国烹饪学院这件事吧
the fact I got into the Culinary Institute of America.
什么  这可是大事
What? Oh, my god, that's huge.
这不可能
That's impossible.
怎么会这样
How did that happen?
我是说  恭喜
I mean, congratulations.
你觉得我该去吗
So, you think I should go?
不该  我是说...
No! I mean...
当然  为什么不呢
yes, why wouldn't you?
考虑到昨天的种种...
Well, starting with yesterday...
考虑到我们
because of us.
不是说我们已经在一起了
Not that we're already an "us,"
只是感觉我们正朝着这个方向进行
but I feels like we might be going in an "us" direction.
真好  我也是这么感觉的
That's really sweet. I feel that, too.
但你知道我还有什么感觉吗
Um, but you know what I also feel?
比如我想知道...
Curious as to...
你两天前才决定成为大厨
as to how you got into one of the best schools in the country
为什么就能被全国最好的学校录取
when you just decided you wanted to be a chef, like, two days ago.
所以...
So...
是怎么做到的
how did that happen?
乔什对我有信心  帮我付了学费
Josh really believes in me, and he gave me the money for tuition.
是吗
He did?
是的  为让我录取他还走了后门
Yeah, and he had to pull some strings to get me in.
走后门哈
Pulling strings, is he?
是  我根本没提过
Yeah, I didn't even ask him.
他就很兴奋地要我去上学
He's just so excited for me to go
还为我打理好了一切
that he came up with the whole plan himself.
打理好了一切哈
Coming up with plans, is he?
不得不说  他简直太棒了
What can I say? He's an amazing guy.
是吗
Is he?
真的吗
你看到我们俩亲亲了
You saw us kiss.
这是你对杰克突如其来的
That's the only explanation
这一系列安排的唯一理由
for your big sudden gesture to Jake.
-加比  -别叫我
- Gabi... - Don't Gabi me! Okay?
你求了我两天
You've been asking me for two days
让我带一下他  教他怎么烹饪
to take him on and teach him how to cook,
现在突然要把他送到四千公里外
And now you suddenly want to send him 3,000 miles away?
有意思  乔什
Interesting, Josh.
真有意思
Real interesting.
是吗
Is it?
他想学习  你教他
He wanted to learn, you taught him,
他有了进步  现在可以更上一层楼
He showed progress, and how he's moved on.
别给我讲道理
Don't make sense.
对我没用
That doesn't work with me.
肯定不止这样
I know something's up.
真的吗  比如呢
Oh, really? Like what?
比如你看到我和杰克在一起  你嫉妒
Like, you saw me with Jake and you got jealous.
嫉妒吗  加比  我都替你脸红
Jealous? Gabi, I'm almost embarrassed for you.
我做这些全是因为我关心我弟弟
I did this because I care about my brother,
我以为你会很开心的
and I thought you'd be happy.
现在你就可以一个人处理婚礼的事情
Now you get to work on the wedding yourself,
这不是你一直希望的吗
which is what you wanted.
所以  比起冲着无辜的我大呼小叫
So instead of screaming at the innocent party here...
不如去把精力放在那件事上
Moi-- why don't you try focusing on that?
你说得对
Okay, okay. You're right.
埃兰和艾略特的婚礼是当下最重要的事
Alan and Elliot are the most important thing right now.
婚礼取消
The wedding's off!
为什么全世界都要这样对我
Why does everything happen to me?
小加加
Hey, Gabala.
感谢帮我把我的东西从艾略特那里拿回来
Thanks for bringing my stuff from Elliot's place here.
我无法忍受去顶楼  看到他的脸
I couldn't bear to go to the penthouse and see his face.
还差一步
Okay, one more step...
然后...
and...
加比家吗
Gabi's?
乔什  你说我们要去牛排馆
Josh, you said we're going to a steak house,
不是奇葩馆
not god's mistake house.
他为什么会在这里
What's he doing here?
天呐  这是个圈套
Oh, my god, this is a set up!
惊喜
Surprise!
不管你们在计划什么
I don't know what you two are planning,
都不会有效的
but it's not gonna work.
-童话世界  -魔力梦幻
- It's like a fairy tale! - Pure enchantment!
你以为我会考虑
To think I would even consider
嫁给一个又自私又事儿逼的人
marrying someone so selfish and dramatic.
我事儿逼吗
Oh, I'm dramatic?
拜托
Puhleeze!
我做的一切都是为了我们的婚礼能够完美
All I was trying to do was make our wedding perfect.
没错  "我们的婚礼"
Exactly! "Our wedding."
你完全没把我考虑进去
You didn't include me at all.
我曾经深爱的那个浪漫的人去哪里了
What happened to the romantic man I fell in love with?
你把我逼的都开始暴饮暴食了
You're making me stress eat.
这什么鬼
What the hell is this?
天呐  你找到戒指了...
Oh, my god! You found the ring...
正如埃兰计划的一样
that Alan planted.
永远爱你  我的FMB
"Forever, my FMB."
毛茸茸的面包球
Fluffy matzo ball.
我知道为了这次的婚礼  我有些疯狂
I know I went a little crazy with the wedding,
但我从未忘记过你
but I would never forget you.
我爱你  毛茸茸的面包球
I love you, fluffy matzo ball.
我也爱你  我的犹太小甘薯
And I love you, my yiddish yam.
想离开这里吗
Wanna get outta here?
从踏进来就想了
Since the moment I walked in.
难以置信你的计划居然成功了
I can't believe your plan worked!
没有你  我肯定搞不定
Yeah, well, I couldn't have done it without you.
把戒指藏在肉馅饼里这招  简直...
And planting the ring in the pot pie, I mean...
干得漂亮
nice touch!
我俩配合很默契
We are a good team.
没错
I guess we are.
浪费了这美妙的旋律会遗憾的
Be a shame to let this music go to waste, huh?
我能请你跳支舞吗
May I have this dance?
好的
Okay.
加比  有些话我想对你说
Gabi, there's something I want to tell you.
我也有话对你说
There's something I want to tell you, too.
过去的这几天有些疯狂
These past couple of days have been kinda crazy,
同时也令我也变得狂躁
and they've made me kinda crazy, and...
我指责你嫉妒我
I accused you of being jealous,
但其实你做的一切
when, really, all you were doing was
都是为你弟弟好
looking out for your brother, so...
是我错怪你了
I'm really sorry.
该你说了
Okay, your turn.
加比...
Gabi...
我一定要赶他走的真正原因是...
The real reason I wanted my brother to go away...
因为我对你还...
is because I think I have...
-怎么...  -加比
-What the... - Gabi!
加比  出来
Gabi, come out here!
天呐
Oh, my god!
加比和杰克的餐车
那是我弟弟吗
Is that my brother?
看我给你准备了什么
Look at what I got for us!
乔什  我不去烹饪学院了
Oh, hey, Josh! I'm not going to the Culinary Institute.
我为我和加比弄了一辆餐车
I got this food truck for me and Gabi instead!
我的名字还在上面
It's got my name on it!
-什么鬼...  -爱死啦
- What a piece of... - I love it!
戒指就该在这周围
The ring has to be here.
其他地方我都看过了
I've looked everywhere else.
沙发你看了吗
Well, did you check the couch?
天呐  一百块
My god! $100!
比我整个沙发的价值都高
That's more than my whole couch is worth.
给自己提个醒
Note to self,
开始清理沙发
start cleaning the couch.
我们应该花在值得的事情上
We should spend that on something responsible.
-比如付账单吗  -不是
- Like paying bills? - No.
"值得的事情"
"Something responsible"
是我打算下注的马的名字
is the name of the horse I want to bet on.
姐妹  走着
Girl, come on!